Hello everyone, I don't know how to write, I don't know how to write well, mainly based on demonstration, it's a little hard.
This is my self-introduction, last year I came back from Tangping, I stayed at home for a while,
I have been doing this for 20 years, I stayed at some companies,
because I think I put some things in the tower, I participated in some movie business.
I am also interested in A-Zhang, you can pay attention to it.
I don't have a lot of personal things, they are just some things that flow.
And then today,
I would like to share some of my MD skills,
because I feel that I have been using MD since 2010,
just like what he just said, the earliest batch,
because I was the first in Beiji Guang in Tangxun,
I used it in the early days of Tianyang Mingrui Dao.
Then I will talk about some of the characters I played in the previous episode,
and some of the skills I learned.
These are the final effects, and these are some of the things I learned in the MD.
The preparation for the early stages,
because I don't know if there will be some people who play games today,
or some people who make clothes,
I think the game is not the same as the clothes,
we have to consider the process of its use,
rather than a temporary one,
because many people who make MD,
they still make something relatively new.
You see, I will look for some old traces in the early stages,
because the game,
maybe we still have to consider some external problems,
consider some of these life-threatening things.
And then this is basically two days,
I won't talk about it,
because what I just said is,
now Marble has the official material called Connect,
it is that,
there are a lot of free things in the official market,
such as basic T-shirts, basic hats,
there are all kinds of boards,
like these,
it may be through some very basic boards of these pants,
because I do things,
I like to do it from the whole,
so I make a very basic pair of pants,
and then I go a little bit more,
because a lot of people I see,
because I will also have classes,
I will learn a lot,
I will do it from small details,
I feel that I have to start from the whole,
and then from little by little,
to take it apart,
or not to say that at the beginning,
I will make my board into something,
because it will be very difficult.
And then you see,
the hobby of the game is to need a lot of this outline,
details,
because like these little things,
like these little things,
I personally like to do it in Marble,
because a lot of people like to pick it up in the later stages,
but I think,
I will,
in terms of MD,
it will take a lot of time,
at the end,
it will take a little bit of time,
to do a little bit of things,
and then a lot of people like to do it,
through that kind of pin,
those big things,
to fix these things,
I think it will be too deliberate,
I mean,
it will look particularly dead,
including some cat-like things,
and then I will,
I mainly show it,
and then,
and then it's the most basic,
because a lot of people go to do MD,
it's almost the same,
I think it will be OK,
for me,
I think,
in terms of games,
there will be a lot of strange things,
that is,
not very comfortable,
so this piece,
I will use a,
a double-layer concept,
that is,
then what it gives me,
I will give it a double layer,
There are some people who like to directly send it to the right-hand side or can create a kind of inside of this column.
Because for me, the column will put all the lines together.
So I usually ask him, I will give him a little bit, and then I will give him, let's say,
Let's say I will give him a little bit of the line.
Then I will connect it to the inside.
And then I will flip it over.
Then he will hold his hat up.
But this is definitely not enough.
This one, this one, this one, this one, this one, this one, this one, this one, this one, this one, this one, this one.
For this one, I guess a lot of people are the same.
But I think MD can change its shape.
You can do it a little bit by hand.
It has a gesture.
You see, this one is a little bit strange for the game.
Its composition is because it is a triangle.
I think the gesture is based on the change of the face.
I will give it to him.
If I say, I will add this one.
The content line.
I will give it to him.
See, when I add a line, it will have some effect on your mouth.
I will say, I will.
add a curve here.
You see, I will add a lot of internal lines to this.
Some people may find it strange when they make clothes, so I will add a lot of internal lines to change the shape.
You see, I can control all the folds, including the shape here.
I can control it with the internal lines to make it more accurate.
You see, I added a lot of internal lines here.
Because many people like to add internal lines to clothes and models.
I will control the shape of the clothes.
Because many people like to take these things with them, so they can turn around.
But for me, I can add a lot of internal lines.
You see, I am adding a lot of internal lines to the clothes.
You can change the distance.
For example, I am making a cuirass for her.
You see, she'll open up the cuirass.
If I do this...
She'll open up the cuirass.
I can open up.
Open up?
You can control all the shapes, you can add a lot, for example, left and right, front and back are all controllable.
For example, some of the movements I just mentioned are all controllable, and sometimes they are not for the project.
For the game project, we hope that the joints have some movements, and we can use this method to control them.
Because the game is not like a costume or a movie,
you can control the game in real time.
For example, if my character keeps running, I can control the movements.
A lot of people can do a lot of movements,
because if you move your arm, it looks more comfortable.
This is just a small tip.
But I will talk about some simple tips today.
Is there any problem here?
No, I don't think so.
And this is the hat.
Because you can control the shape of the hat,
it is not for the project.
Because in this way, it will ensure that I have a good appearance,
whether it is a costume or a costume,
because it is relatively good-looking.
It is not for a lot of people.
For example, if you lie down,
it is not very good for your side appearance.
And then for the pants, it is also a principle.
For the pants, you see,
I just mentioned that I like to add some small details to this kind of small details.
Because many times,
you have to consider the things we wear,
there will be some small edges,
there will be some small things,
and then I will use this kind of...
this kind of...
And then you see,
you can control its pull,
its external or external impact.
Because in this way,
black.
Because for the use,
for the game,
more of us hope that this will not be broken.
Because what I see is a screenshot.
I hope it is good for the screenshot.
So I added some of these little tips
to make it more interesting,
to make it more vivid,
to make it more image-oriented.
And then I have some...
In fact,
in the end,
I added some effects to the big toe.
You see,
it will be more interesting.
Compared to the usual,
if you don't add it,
it will naturally be broken.
You see,
it is too flat for your outline.
For me,
for the game,
it is too flat.
Because the game,
after all,
we use very few faces,
so you achieve a very good effect.
So this kind of place
becomes very interesting.
This kind of place
And then there is another one
that I often use,
which is the inner line.
Because many people use the inner line,
which is...
I feel that it is...
Just add a little bit
of this roughness.
But for me,
I will add it very strongly.
For example,
this effect.
This effect.
I don't know if you can see it clearly.
Can you see it clearly?
Yes.
Very good.
Look.
This effect.
It has this structure.
I use the inner line
to simulate it.
You see,
I will add this inner line.
This line.
I will simulate it.
This can be done
just by using
two simple inner lines.
I will draw two inner lines.
And then I will choose a straight line.
Because the inner line
can adjust the angle.
Adjust the strength
and adjust the angle.
This straight line.
The smaller the angle of the fold,
it will go out.
And then the larger the angle of the fold,
it will go inside.
So,
look at me.
For this line,
I will go out.
For the next line,
I will go inside.
In this way,
you will get
this kind of
interesting effect.
And if it is not strong,
you will add this kind of
large line
to pull it up
and it will be
more interesting.
You see,
like this,
I will
go inside.
Like this,
I will go out
with this.
Actually,
you have to know
that
you have to use
some small techniques
to make
your things
more vivid.
Maybe
FD has been developing
a lot of
things
that
you can
draw
with
FD.
But,
I feel that
what I am using
is still
the most basic
of things.
And then,
I will
add some
of this kind of
memory marks
at the end.
For many people,
this kind of
memory marks
are used
to add
to these
things
through
FD.
For example,
this kind of
reference
for me
will be
added
to this kind
of memory marks
including
the back
of the knees
because
it is bent.
It will have
this kind of
memory marks.
Especially,
our women's pants
and
our
underwear
will have
some
effects.
It is all
done
through
this
internal line
and then
we will
add this
to the
back of the knees
to make it
more
alive.
When I was
on the
stage,
I was
doing
Li An's
...
When it comes to
Before we do this, I need to replace Windows and Linux 4.0, because JPEG doesn't have Linux 4.0 yet.
For some people, this is the ultimate solution.
If we have a high demand for the camera, we can make it a little bit more comfortable.
If it is a tablet, it may not be that interesting.
Maybe when we are doing it, it will give us a little bit of comfort.
We can make it a little bit more comfortable.
It is not too difficult.
Why does it become more interesting?
Many people have tried this.
I think the edge will have this kind of pressure edge effect.
Actually, I also realized it through this kind of internal line.
I will make a few edges, and then I will make a kind of hollowed out one.
It will give it a more interesting effect.
These places are all designed to be like this.
The inner line is designed to be like this.
This is how you will make it hollow out.
And then this hollowed out edge, I will also...
Usually, we make three lines, two sides.
This is common.
It is to make it hollow out.
If you make it single, it will be hollowed out, and the back will be shaped, and it will have some effects.
Thank you.
This is the final effect of the hollowed out edge.
And then this is the final effect of the hollowed out edge.
You see, I will add some inner lines, and then adjust the intensity to get the final effect.
Because with this version, I will adjust the resolution to about 2 or 3.
Because with this version, I won't need to go and stopped with DB anymore.
I will do a rematch.
And then I will go and restart with DB.
And then I will do a rematch.
The technique will be the same.
I will just add some techniques to get a lot of perfect results.
This is the final effect.
I will then add all the inner lines to control my movement.
All of these are controlled by these inner lines.
I think that FB can update it to, uh...
Because the internal line can only be generated in one direction, but the clock can be divided into two directions.
So this can be adjusted, including this one.
Look, I added a lot of internal lines to make it more interesting.
It's almost like this.
I may speak a little faster.
This is the final effect.
Then I will finish it.
This is a very complicated solution.
There are a lot of major versions.
Thank you.
This is the end.
Do you have any questions?
Yes.
Any questions?
No.
How about the rice, is it good?
Thank you.
I have two questions.
I went to a small studio today, and I saw that there was a water-based cloth on the water-based cloth.
Because it is water-based, there are also some wrinkles on the cloth.
Should I adjust it to the internal line?
The internal line can be adjusted.
But it is better to still look at some references.
Because I found that many people can do it.
But they hope that my wrinkles will be better and better.
In terms of art, for me, I think you have to do it carefully.
You have to learn some rhythm.
For example, when I do this kind of embroidery,
for example, my wrinkles are a little less and then a little more.
But there is something like this.
You will let him observe more about life.
Because a lot of people do mb, they think it is very difficult.
Mb is a material that can be solved.
The more wrinkles, the better.
Because the more, the more annoying it becomes.
In fact, it becomes bad.
Thank you.
When you make a game, for example,
when you make these kind of games,
do you use mb?
Yes.
Because in the game, all the wrinkles are dead.
There is no way to actually solve them, right?
I will calculate everything.
Everything is my final.
But for movies,
because you just watched Hobbit or Ding Ding,
those things,
it has a basic shape.
Because all movies,
we call it DTW.
And then I will have an actor,
he will have a scan model for us.
We have to do our mb things
and scan things
are too much different.
So my movie is one,
for example, I make a movie action.
Because your character
has to play this pose a little bit.
We have to do it to this extent.
And then let him have a dynamic real-time calculation.
So that's it.
Maybe we need to make our model
more similar to his scan model.
At least my feeling is almost the same.
I'm just talking about the feeling.
It's your beat and what you want to do.
It's a little bit different from him.
Because in the end,
everything has to be re-calculated.
And then you have to make sure
that everything can't be different.
Everything has to be a little bit different.
Including some of the videos on the body.
There are some things that have to be checked.
I think in terms of the game,
maybe Google technology will be a little bit more.
Because you need to do a little bit of rematch.
To brush, to do the first film, to prepare.
But in this case,
for example, we made a version of MD.
And then I need to rematch it.
And then to give it a little bit more.
Increase the thickness.
Increase the width.
Increase the width of this small curve.
And then divide it into UV.
You don't have to prepare anything.
You make the model look good.
And then you see this kind of sticker.
They just change the stickers.
It's going to be a little bit easier.
But you need to do this.
All the details on the clothes.
Just look at the lens of your lens.
Think about it.
I need to do a play.
Do a little bit of work.
It's like this.
Just help me.
Any other questions?
Hello, teacher.
The teacher wants to ask you something.
That is to say, we went to MD.
To do the digital animation.
In addition to the professional workers of the Chinese Academy of Arts,
There is an art school.
For example, if we wear clothes, our hands will be covered with clothes.
If we wear clothes, our hands and clothes will be covered with clothes.
Now there is such a thing.
For example, if I forcefully increase the density of the clothes,
then its resolution will be relatively low.
If the density is relatively low,
then my hands and clothes will be covered with clothes.
I think this animation has a very wide range.
When we were doing it,
although I think Vita is a very top-notch company in the world,
but when he went to do the calculation,
he was still using Maya's encode.
Now, because it is more likely to use some Houdini,
there will be an agent model.
Because we also went to do Syngeo,
our Syngeo is still very fine.
For example, when we do this kind of calculation model,
it is about a density of 6 to 8 in AMD.
So we forcefully give them this.
But my Vita model must be much thinner than this.
It's almost the same.
Because if I say that this model of mine
is about 6,
they will use this kind of density to solve it.
It's still very thin.
I don't know if they will like it or not.
But what we usually provide is this density.
I think there is not much feedback in general.
Sometimes they will use some internal software to rematch it.
But I don't think this density is almost the same as this density.
I don't know what they will do with some agent models.
Because this is something that other companies do well.
The movie will be very detailed.
I don't remember it very well.
Thank you.
Hello, thank you.
I would like to add something.
Don't be in a hurry to sit down.
I see you are about to fall.
Because the MP can now give the animation key.
I don't know if you have seen it.
No, I haven't.
It should be that you haven't seen it.
Yes, I have.
Because I talked about how to fix this hand in the live broadcast.
There won't be any interference in the other parts.
Because it is now possible to play the key point of animation.
So we will usually be under that point.
Generally, this hand interference is from a certain point.
It sticks to the top.
Yes.
Then when there is a needle in the back.
It will suddenly loosen itself up.
Or it is no longer interference.
Then we will return the animation to the point of interference.
Then freeze all the panels.
Only leave the panel of interference.
Then first of all, if you want to be lazy.
You can start from the beginning.
Maybe it will hook to the position of this panel.
Separate the area.
Just separate this area.
This can save the number of points.
But many times.
At that time.
Everyone will think.
Then I don't want to use the point of interference.
You just go back to that point.
Then in that point.
Isn't it that all the other panels are frozen?
You are alone.
Don't turn on the animation under that point.
Directly in that point.
You can use a fixed point.
Or another way.
Separate the position of the interference from it.
Or hit the fixed point directly.
Fix this panel to one side.
For example, on the wrist.
I'm sorry.
You said it was the neck.
That is near the neck position.
Or the finger position.
Let him not penetrate.
Then from this point.
The few points after that.
May penetrate.
Don't turn on the animation.
All in that point.
It's because when we record.
There is already a live animation.
Already recorded.
Right?
That section.
Other positions.
He is normal.
So each point.
In the case of that point.
Freeze the other parts.
Only leave the position of interference.
Then delete the key point of that point.
Delete.
You finished recording.
Delete the key point of that point.
Delete.
You finished recording.
Then erase.
Now.
Louta is stable.
I hav not Trek to the situation.
A Ésdko back.
Then.
The next time.
Rule.
Say there is
ten stitches.
There are chain stitches.
This ten stitches.
You are active.
Can you take a stab.
It is unexpected.
Only end of infinite needle.
Let him out of it.
In the middle.
Because we will have the linear change.
You can just bloody go.
I'll check it, okay? I must see your comments below
I'm not advertising